<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>legacy on</title><link>https://corvusdeinanis.github.io/cuddly-train/tags/legacy/</link><description>Recent content in legacy on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://corvusdeinanis.github.io/cuddly-train/tags/legacy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Culture and Socialization</title><link>https://corvusdeinanis.github.io/cuddly-train/Culture-and-Socialization/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://corvusdeinanis.github.io/cuddly-train/Culture-and-Socialization/</guid><description>Culture -agency of social change -total design for living -social heritage transmitted from one generation to another -sum total of materials and intellectual equipments by which we satisfy needs Etymology of Culture Colere - Latin word - cultivate / till the soil Etymology Malinowski handiwork of man; medium through which man achieves his ends Definition Edward B Tyler complex whole which includes knowledge, beliefs, arts, law, customs, language, morals, and any other capabilities acq by man as a member of society Definition Characteristics of Culture Learnt, social, shared, transmissive, relative, dynamic, gratifying, continuous, ideanational [DISC STRGL] Mnemonic Culture is learnt not inborn, it is learnt, transmitted, learnt through socialization and group life; ex shaking hands, clothing, worshipping, saying thanks, etc characteristics Culture is social social heritage of man, group life, social interaction.</description></item><item><title>Medieval Ages</title><link>https://corvusdeinanis.github.io/cuddly-train/Medieval-Ages/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://corvusdeinanis.github.io/cuddly-train/Medieval-Ages/</guid><description>Henry IV King; appoints Bishop of Milan without Pope&amp;rsquo;s permission, fought with Gregory VII Philip IV French King; taxed church without permission of Pope; fought with Boniface VIII St Peter First Pope Gregory The Great Pope becomes the most powerful; Establishes Papacy Gregory VII Pope; wanted to free Church from King, fought with Henry IV Gregory XI Pope, shifts court back to Rome Boniface VIII Pope; goes against Philip IV, beaten to death Clement V Pope who replaces Boniface VIII, moves court to Avignon Urban VI Pope; differences between him and cardinals led to election of anti-pope and caused papal schism Clement VII Anti-Pope, moves court back to Avignon Alexander V Anti-Pope, to replace Clement VII and Urban VI 1414 CE Papal schism ended 500 - 1050 CE Early Middle Age / Dark Ages 1050 - 1300 CE High Middle Age 1300 - 1453 CE Later Middle Age 476 CE Western Roman Empire falls 1453 CE Eastern Roman Empire falls Ecclesiastical System Manoral System Medieval Society in brief Agriculture in Medieval society First - low due to political instability, wars, etc.</description></item><item><title>Modern Age</title><link>https://corvusdeinanis.github.io/cuddly-train/Modern-Age/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://corvusdeinanis.github.io/cuddly-train/Modern-Age/</guid><description>14th - 17th Century Modern Age, distinct urban culture in Europe date Centers of art and learning Florence, Venice, and Rome Patronised Artists and Writers by rich and aristocratic Printing Important invention.</description></item><item><title>Radio Summary</title><link>https://corvusdeinanis.github.io/cuddly-train/Radio-Summary/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://corvusdeinanis.github.io/cuddly-train/Radio-Summary/</guid><description>Radio typically with frequencies of 300 gigahertz (GHz) and below. cheapest form of entertainment accessibility and availability allowed information to be transmitted quickly and uniformly to vast populations World Wars</description></item><item><title>Social Change</title><link>https://corvusdeinanis.github.io/cuddly-train/Social-Change/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://corvusdeinanis.github.io/cuddly-train/Social-Change/</guid><description>Social Change All social phenomena exhibit change over a period of time.</description></item><item><title>Social Institutions</title><link>https://corvusdeinanis.github.io/cuddly-train/Social-Institutions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://corvusdeinanis.github.io/cuddly-train/Social-Institutions/</guid><description>Marriage important and universal social institution that governs sexual relationships Marriage according to Robert H Lowie permanent bond between permissible mates Aim of marriage procreational, companionship, psychological support Aim of marriage ii used to be social obligation.</description></item><item><title>World Revolutions</title><link>https://corvusdeinanis.github.io/cuddly-train/World-Revolutions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://corvusdeinanis.github.io/cuddly-train/World-Revolutions/</guid><description>Revolution Complete change. Fundamental change in organisational structures in a rel short period of time Etymology of Revolution Revolutio, Latin for complete change etymology 1750 - 1917 Revolutions in Europe and America, rise of nationalism Change in social, political and economic setup date 1750 - 1850 Industrial Revolution date Industrial Revolution Changes in agriculture, manufacturing, mining and transportation, and technology.</description></item><item><title>World Wars</title><link>https://corvusdeinanis.github.io/cuddly-train/World-Wars/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://corvusdeinanis.github.io/cuddly-train/World-Wars/</guid><description>World War 1 World War 2 Cold War Cold War Course of Events 1 Agressive Nationalism Dictatorship Refusal of Russia to evac Iran Truman Doctrine 2 Role of Newspapers - Sovietization of East Europe Marshall Plan - Failure of League Of Nations 3 Arms Race Rearmament Soviet Influence in Greece Molotov Plan 4 Imperialism and Economic Rivalry (Germany vs England) Colonial and Commercial Rivalry Soviet Influence in Turkey Berlin Blockade 5 Balkan Problems (Russia vs Austria) Expansionist policies Problems related to Germany Civil War in Korea 6 Military Alliances Treaty of Versailes Secrecy of Atom Bomb Warsaw Pact 7 Immediate Cause (Assn.</description></item><item><title>Sem V Bucket</title><link>https://corvusdeinanis.github.io/cuddly-train/Sem-V-Bucket/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://corvusdeinanis.github.io/cuddly-train/Sem-V-Bucket/</guid><description>Literature Gender and Literature Locating Gender Gender: View from the margins Gender Identities and the Everyday Gender through Lens Blue book</description></item><item><title>Sem IV Cloud Computing Syllabus</title><link>https://corvusdeinanis.github.io/cuddly-train/Cloud-Computing-Syllabus-Legacy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://corvusdeinanis.github.io/cuddly-train/Cloud-Computing-Syllabus-Legacy/</guid><description>(this is a legacy file; included for posterity)
Module 1 [[What is Cloud Computing]]
Principles of Parallel and Distributed Computing [[Parallel vs Distributed Computing]]</description></item></channel></rss>